The once-famous illusionist troupe of Luoyang City
فرقة الوهم ذات مرة في مدينة لويانغ
mysteriously disappeared.
اختفى في ظروف غامضة.
Their most famous performance was
كان أداءهم الأكثر شهرة
the Flaming Parrot.
الببغاء المشتعل.
An illusionist act.
فعل الوهم.
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
After they vanished,
بعد اختفوا ،
it's highly likely they were used by Sun Chengjing.
من المحتمل جدًا أن يتم استخدامها بواسطة Sun Chengjing.
They took part in creating the phoenix omen.
شاركوا في إنشاء فينيكس فأل.
And after the omen incident,
وبعد حادث الفأل ،
they disappeared again.
اختفوا مرة أخرى.
At the time, I suspected
في ذلك الوقت ، اشتبهت
they were probably silenced.
ربما تم إسكاتهم.
But now it seems
ولكن يبدو الآن
there are still survivors.
لا يزال هناك ناجون.
And this survivor
وهذا الناجي
is the handyman at Fulai Restaurant.
هو العانين في مطعم فولاي.
No wonder.
لا عجب.
The restaurant waiter was just an accomplice they recruited.
كان نادل المطعم مجرد شريك قاموا بتجنيده.
The handyman was responsible for creating the phoenix illusion.
كان العاملون مسؤولاً عن إنشاء وهم فينيكس.
Someone else was in charge of killing.
كان شخص آخر مسؤولاً عن القتل.
And moving the bodies.
ونقل الجثث.
So,
لذا،
catching one or two people is useless.
اصطياد شخص أو شخصين لا طائل منه.
We need to catch everyone involved in this incident
نحن بحاجة إلى التقاط كل المشاركين في هذا الحادث
in one fell swoop.
في ضربة واحدة.
Brother Jianxing,
الأخ جيانكينغ ،
I still need your help.
ما زلت بحاجة إلى مساعدتك.
I suspect
أظن
they have an underground secret room.
لديهم غرفة سرية تحت الأرض.
I need you to find this secret room.
أريدك أن تجد هذه الغرفة السرية.
Sir
سيد
I remember your favorite food is roast chicken, isn't it?
أتذكر طعامك المفضل هو الدجاج المشوي ، أليس كذلك؟
Actually,
في الحقيقة،
if I hadn't caught that bald chicken,
إذا لم أكن قد اشتعلت هذا الدجاج الأصلع ،
you wouldn't have discovered there was something wrong with this warehouse.
لن تكتشف أن هناك خطأ ما في هذا المستودع.
Right?
يمين؟
Even if I didn't achieve much, I still put in the effort.
حتى لو لم أحقق الكثير ، ما زلت أبذل الجهد.
I promise
أعدك
I absolutely won't gamble again.
أنا على الإطلاق لن أقامر مرة أخرى.
So, in that case,
لذلك ، في هذه الحالة ،
that bald chicken deserves a lot of credit.
هذا الدجاج الأصلع يستحق الكثير من الائتمان.
Are you comparing me to a bald chicken?
هل تقارنني بدجاج أصلع؟
Quiet, we're handling official business.
هادئ ، نحن نتعامل مع الأعمال الرسمية.
Steward, wake up.
ستيوارد ، استيقظ.
Sir has questions for you.
سيدي لديه أسئلة لك.
Sir is dead.
سيدي ميت.
It seems our guess was correct.
يبدو أن تخميننا كان صحيحا.
We just arrived a bit too late.
لقد وصلنا للتو قليلاً.
What should we do now?
ماذا يجب أن نفعل الآن؟
Then we'll have to ask him.
ثم علينا أن نسأله.
Come out.
يخرج.
Murder! Someone's been killed!
قتل! قتل شخص ما!
There's been a murder!
كان هناك جريمة قتل!
Someone's been killed!
قتل شخص ما!
Don't be nervous.
لا تكن عصبيا.
What did you see?
ماذا رأيت؟
I saw someone
رأيت شخصًا ما
kill the steward.
اقتل المضيفة.
Who was it?
من كان؟
I-I didn't see clearly.
الثاني لم ير بوضوح.
It was in a courtyard.
كان في فناء.
Are you sure you didn't see anything clearly?
هل أنت متأكد من أنك لم ترى أي شيء بوضوح؟
Don't kill me, please don't kill me!
لا تقتلني ، من فضلك لا تقتلني!
I really didn't see anything clearly!
أنا حقا لم أر أي شيء بوضوح!
Don't make things difficult for him.
لا تجعل الأمور صعبة بالنسبة له.
If he had seen the killer clearly,
إذا كان قد رأى القاتل بوضوح ،
he'd have ended up like the steward by now.
لقد انتهى به الأمر مثل ستيوارد الآن.
So, sir,
لذلك يا سيدي ،
what should we do now?
ماذا يجب أن نفعل الآن؟
We'll have to trouble Brother Jianxing for help.
سيتعين علينا أن نزعج الأخ Jianxing طلبًا للمساعدة.
Strange.
غريب.
Since there's a smell of blood in the courtyard,
نظرًا لوجود رائحة دم في الفناء ،
I should be able to smell it.
يجب أن أكون قادرًا على شمها.
Unless...
إلا إذا...
Unless what?
ما لم يكن؟
Unless the entrance to the secret room is downwind.
ما لم يكن مدخل الغرفة السرية في اتجاه الريح.
That way, when the wind blows,
بهذه الطريقة ، عندما تهب الرياح ،
the smell of blood would be dispersed.
سوف تشتت رائحة الدم.
At this time of year,
في هذا الوقت من العام ،
the wind in Luoyang comes from the southeast.
الريح في لويانغ تأتي من الجنوب الشرقي.
Then the entrance to the secret room
ثم مدخل الغرفة السرية
must be in the northwest.
يجب أن يكون في الشمال الغربي.
The smell of fresh grass
رائحة العشب الطازج
The scent of camphor wood
رائحة كامبور وود
The smell of blood
رائحة الدم
Right there
هناك
Yes
نعم
This is the Red-feathered Chicken
هذا هو الدجاج الأحمر ريد
Sir
سيد
Isn't this the phoenix I caught before?
أليس هذا هو فينيكس الذي اشتعلت من قبل؟
Did you see anything?
هل رأيت أي شيء؟
Divine blood and fire
الدم الإلهي والنار
Illuminates the heavens
يضيء السماوات
May we be blessed by this light
نرجو أن نكون مباركين بهذا الضوء
May it last forever
قد تستمر إلى الأبد
What nonsense about holy blood
يا له من هراء عن الدم المقدس
A bunch of scoundrels
حفنة من الأوغاد
Protect the holy blood
حماية الدم المقدس
Kill them for me
اقتلهم من أجلي
Come on, whoever wants to die, come first
تعال ، من يريد أن يموت ، تعال أولاً
Blood oath to the sacred land, may the gods bless our faith
يمين الدم إلى الأرض المقدسة ، قد يبارك الآلهة إيماننا
This is a test from the gods
هذا اختبار من الآلهة
Zeng Sheng, save the people first
Zeng Sheng ، أنقذ الناس أولاً
Understood
مفهومة
Sir
سيد
How is it?
كيف هذا؟
Still alive.
لا يزال على قيد الحياة.
Still trying to run?
ما زلت تحاول الجري؟
Listen carefully to my questions.
استمع بعناية إلى أسئلتي.
Who is behind all this?
من وراء كل هذا؟
Where does the blood poison come from?
من أين يأتي سم الدم؟
What are you doing with so much blood?
ماذا تفعل مع الكثير من الدم؟
I won't say anything.
لن أقول أي شيء.
Looking for death?
تبحث عن الموت؟
Wait.
انتظر.
Brother Jianxing
الأخ جيانكينغ
You're asking so many questions at once.
أنت تسأل الكثير من الأسئلة في وقت واحد.
How can he answer like that?
كيف يمكن أن يجيب هكذا؟
I'll just ask you one thing.
سأطلب منك شيئًا واحدًا فقط.
Why are you taking so much blood?
لماذا تأخذ الكثير من الدم؟
You're asking me here,
أنت تسألني هنا ،
should I tell you,
هل يجب أن أخبرك ،
or should I not tell you?
أم لا يجب أن أخبرك؟
Should I tell you the truth,
هل يجب أن أقول لك الحقيقة ،
or should I lie to you?
أم يجب أن أكذب عليك؟
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
I get a little dizzy at the sight of blood.
أحصل على القليل من الدوار في مشهد الدم.
What do you mean by that, talking so strangely?
ماذا تقصد بذلك ، تتحدث بشكل غريب؟
You might as well just tell the truth.
قد تخبر الحقيقة فقط.
Are you going to talk or not?
هل ستتحدث أم لا؟
If you won't talk,
إذا لم تتحدث ،
don't blame me for being rough with you.
لا تلومني على أن أكون تقريبيًا معك.
I've already devoted myself to the gods.
لقد كرست نفسي بالفعل للآلهة.
Why would I fear life or death?
لماذا أخاف الحياة أو الموت؟
Don't waste your energy.
لا تضيع طاقتك.
You're not afraid of dying.
أنت لا تخاف من الموت.
Fine.
بخير.
What about them?
ماذا عنهم؟
If he won't talk, then you tell me.
إذا لم يتحدث ، فأنت تخبرني.
Why did you kill people and take their blood?
لماذا قتلت الناس وأخذت دمائهم؟
Burn my broken body in the blazing holy fire.
حرق جسدي المكسور في النار المقدسة الحارقة.
Shut up.
اسكت.
The divine blood fire will soon engulf the entire land.
سوف نيران الدم الإلهي سرعان ما تبتلع الأرض بأكملها.
You disloyal people,
أيها الناس غير مرغوبون ،
will all turn to ashes.
سوف يتحول جميع إلى الرماد.
Hold down his hand.
امسك يده.
He's dead.
لقد مات.